(Leonard:)...trapped your knight in the corner,
and you keep sighing and saying:
"Why me?"
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)Can I ask you a question
about women?
(Leonard:)We got you that book last year.
Wasn't everything in there?
(Sheldon:)No. I'm having
a relationship problem with Amy.
(Sheldon:)And by the way,
that book gave me nightmares.
(Leonard:)If it makes you feel any better...
...l screwed things up pretty good
with Penny.
(Sheldon:)Look at us, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Engaging in the social convention of
men bellyaching about their old ladies.
l guess we are. So...
(Leonard:)What's going on?
(Sheldon:)Believe it or not,
Amy has embarked on a campaign...
(Sheldon:)...to increase my feelings for her
by making me happy.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry,
that must be very difficuIt for you.
(Sheldon:)It's awful. This morning...